（紫原(むらさきばら)）うおおっ
（紫原）どりゃああっ！
（３人）うわっ！
This is reality.
（紫原）これが現実でしょ？
どうあがいても誠凛(せいりん)の負けだよ
No matter how you struggle, Seirin will lose.
I'll never lose to someone like you who denies the efforts of others!
（黒子(くろこ)）人の努力を
否定してしまう君には—
絶対 負けたくない！
（紫原）うっ この高さで
ボールに触れない！？
I can't touch the ball at this height?
（氷室(ひむろ)）あっ 敦(あつし)！
Atsushi!
It's a pass!
パスだ！
（火神(かがみ)）えい！
Like Murasakibara, I'll cover the entire two point area.
（火神）
オレが紫原と同じように—
ツーポイントエリア全域を
カバーする
No matter who comes, I'll stop them.
誰が来ようとオレが止める！
For Kiyoshi.
木吉(きよし)先輩の分まで！
shoudou ga atte usoppachi ni idonde
I've got the urge to challenge these bold-faced lies.
boku to kimi to ga shujinkou Love song
You and I are the stars of this love song.
dondon ikimashou
It's time to pick up the pace
Translation Checking: AMS
tsuyoki de semeraretanda
before I lose out to some go-getter,
nakamauchi no warai banashi de wa
and end up like the guys my friends joke about.
Editing: AMS
monmon toshitenda ze
It's starting to drive me crazy...
jibun no heya itsu datte
Always cooped up in my room.
Timing: sangofe
honto wa yowaki na peach mind
The truth is, I've got a timid peach mind
K-Timing: Eternal Blizzard
ki no aru soburi ka
Does she have a thing for me?
Typesetting: AMS, KmE
Karaoke: KmE
tada no omoikomi ka
Or am I reading too much into it?
baretenda ano ko ni wa
Either way, that girl's got us all figured out.
ganbare otoko no ko
Do your best, boys.
Encoding: Your Mom
kono mama ja sanjuugo renpai
If this keeps up, it'll be 35 straight losses.
kimi dake no boku wa Go to guy
But just for you, I'll be your go-to guy.
he
n
ge
ji
za
i
no
ma
ji
ka
ru
su
ta
a
Phantasmagoric magical star
i
da
na
ru
ma
n
ne
ri
da
t
te
i
ja
na
i
What's wrong with a tried-and-true stereotype?
to
me
ro
a
o
sa
wo
Own up to your own inexperience.
ma
da
mi
chi
nu
ko
i
na
ra
ba
If your love has yet to come full circle,
ze
n
bu
a
ge
ru
ze
I'll give you my all.
ki
mi
ni
chi
ka
u
This I swear to you.
saizen-fansubs.com
Yosen
Seirin
Episode
Enough
Yosen
Seirin
What? Kiyoshi, are you serious?
（土田(うちだ)）え！？
（小金井(こがねい)）ちょっ…
マジかよ 木吉…！？
Yeah. The last two... No, one minute is enough.
最後の２分…
いや １分でいい
何とかオレを
動けるようにしてくれ
I have to play.
You're going back in?
（小金井）
もう一度 出るつもりかよ！？
You can't do something so reckless!
（土田）いくら何でも
そんなムチャは…！
（リコ）分かったわ
（小金井）ちょっ！ カントク！？
Fine.
What? Coach?
Are you sure, Riko?
いいのか？ リコ
何言ってんのよ
What are you talking about?
どうせ止めても
無理やり出るでしょうが
Even if I tried to stop you, you'd force your way in.
So, Tsuchida and Koganei, take care of things.
てわけで 土田君と小金井君
あとよろしく！
What?
Give me three minutes.
３分だけちょうだい
その間だけ 指揮 任せるわ
Lead the team while I'm gone.
（福井(ふくい)）うっ… ああっ！
It's a 2-3 zone!
（荒木(あらき)）これは… ２(ツー)-３(スリー)ゾーン！
They're running the same formation as us?
（福井）ウチと同じ
フォーメーション…！？
Is he trying to cover the entire inside like Atsushi?
（氷室）敦と同じように—
中をすべて
カバーするつもりなのか！？
（火神）
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
Are they afraid of our outside?
（福井）外 警戒してんのか
This formation creates a surprising amount of pressure...
意外とプレッシャーあんな
この陣形は…
Against a normal team, that is!
並のチームだったらな！
（福井）ふっ！
（伊月(いづき)）しまった
Crap!
It's an alley-oop!
（日向(ひゅうが)）これは… アリウープだ！
（火神）紫原！
（紫原）んんっ！
Murasakibara!
All we have to do is pass.
ただパス出しゃあ
それでいいんだよ
なんせ…
After all,
（紫原）ううぅ… ああっ
our center is Murasakibara.
（福井）ウチのセンターは紫原だ
（火神）ぐっ…！
（黒子）火神君！
Kagami!
まさか本気で
１人で止められると思ってんの？
Do you really think you can stop me alone?
Don't be so conceited, Kagami.
のぼせるのも
たいがいにしなよ
火神！
If that's what it takes to win, I'll do it.
やらなきゃ勝てねえってんなら
やってやるさ！
I'll stop you.
ぜってえ止める！
（岡村(おかむら)）おっ…
The Stealth Full-Court Man-to-Man Defense again.
（岡村）
またか… ステルス･オールコート
マンツーマンディフェンス！
フン！
（日向）氷室にボールを渡して
全員 上がった！
Everyone left after giving Himuro the ball.
まさか…
火神とワンオンワンか！？
Is he trying to one-on-one Kagami?
You're not going anywhere!
行かすかよ
Do it, if you can!
やってみな…
やれるもんならな！
Seriously?
（火神）マジかよ…
His fakes are good enough, but he's going even faster now!
フェイクの質はもちろん
ここに来て 数段 速(はえ)え！
Muro-chin, stop!
（紫原）室(むろ)ちん ストップ！
（氷室）なっ！
ハァッ
Hello.
どうも
They switched from full-court to half-court.
（荒木）オールコートから
ハーフコートへ…
Seirin's insisting on using the same formation as us.
誠凛は あくまでも—
ウチと同じフォーメーションで
来るつもりか
Taiga really intends to defend the inside alone.
（氷室）本気で中を
１人で守るつもりらしいな
タイガ
He's as reckless as ever. However...
ムチャなところは相変わらずだ…
だが—
That's not courage.
そんなものは勇敢とは言わない
He's looking down on us!
ナメてるっつうんだよ！
Himuro, pass!
（福井）氷室！ パス！
I hate it.
（氷室）気に入らねえよ！
（日向）くっ… ヤベえ…！
Crap!
You can mark whoever you want,
（氷室）
誰をマークしようと勝手だが—
１人で みんな止めようなんて
虫のいい考えは—
but I hate that you think you can stop everyone yourself!
心底 気に入らねえ！
Kagami!
火神！
The truth behind the Mirage Shot is he's releasing the ball twice!
（火神）
ミラージュシュートの正体…
それは空中で２回ボールを
リリースしてるってことだ
First he jumps and snaps the ball straight in the air at the peak of his jump,
１度目はジャンプして
最高点に達する前に—
スナップをきかせて真上に放る
then he catches the ball and shoots it again.
そして それをキャッチして—
もう一度 打つ
To an ordinary player,
並の選手なら—
it simply looks like he released the ball twice.
ただ ２回放っただけにしか
見えない
However, Himuro's skills are so elegant even his fakes look like real shots.
だが ただのフェイクすら
一瞬 本物に見えるほど—
洗練されたスキルを持つ
氷室がやったときのみ—
When he does it, his first release makes the air shimmer,
１度目のリリースが陽炎(かげろう)を生み—
concealing the ball on his second release.
２度目に放たれた実体を
覆い隠す
つまり止めるためには—
In other words, in order to stop him, I have to delay my block!
ブロックに跳ぶのを
わざとワンテンポ遅らせる
He's figured out the trick behind the shot.
（紫原）こいつ…
シュートのカラクリに
気付いてる！？
（氷室）知ってるよ
I know you know.
バレてることは… ふっ！
He shot the ball on the first release!
１度目のリリース時に
そのまま…！？
Did you think it was just some trick shot?
（氷室）ただの
トリックショットだと思ったか？
I can shoot on either release after seeing how my opponent times his jump.
オレは 相手の跳ぶ
タイミングを見てから—
どちらでも打てる
気付いたところで
意味なんかないんだよ
Knowing how it works is useless.
No one can touch the Mirage Shot.
（ホイッスル）
（氷室）ミラージュシュートは—
誰にも触れられない
I can't win like this, but...
（火神）このままじゃ勝てない…
だが—
If I could just enter the Zone like I did against Aomine...
青峰(あおみね)と戦ったときのように—
“ゾーン”にさえ入れれば…
What is that idiot doing?
（青峰）何やってんだか
あのバカは
What?
（黄瀬(きせ)）おっ
Seirin seems to be hanging on.
何とか食いついてってる
じゃないスか 誠凛
ウチの明日の相手は
どっちになるっスかね？
Who do you think we'll be playing tomorrow?
We still have our game to play.
（笠松(かさまつ)）オレらの試合
まだ残ってんだろ
油断すんな！ シバくぞ
Don't let your guard down! I'll hit you.
（森山(もりやま)）ん…？
誠凛ディフェンス—
Seirin's running a 2-3 zone defense?
２-３ゾーンか？ 珍しいな
How unusual.
（笠松）センターが…
Are they missing their center, Kiyoshi?
木吉がいねえのか？
What's Kagamicchi doing in the middle?
（黄瀬）んで 火神っちが
真ん中…？
にしても 何かあいつ…
And he seems...
The Phantom Shot isn't a guaranteed basket.
（日向）ファントムシュートは
決して必中じゃない
We can't ask him to keep making them.
入れ続けろってのが無理な話だ！
The core of Seirin's offense is collapsing.
（アレックス）誠凛のオフェンスの
要が崩れてきた…
しかも—
And once their full-court defense is broken, they can't do anything.
ディフェンスはオールコートを
突破されたら打つ手なし
At this rate...
このまま行くと…
（紫原）うおりゃっ！
Yosen
Seirin
（土田）点差が開いて来たな
Yosen
Seirin
We're falling behind.
Yosen
Seirin
Just one of them would be exceptional, but they've got two.
（小金井）１人でも
桁外れなのに２人も…
How are we supposed to stop them?
どうすりゃ止められんだ
It's too reckless.
（伊月）やっぱムチャだな
火神は何か勝算があるのか？
Does Kagami have some kind of plan?
It's not that I think he doesn't have a plan,
（黒子）無策ではないと思います
ただ 何となく—
but I get the feeling we can't keep doing this.
このままではダメな気がします
What an idiot.
（青峰）ったくバカ野郎が
At this rate, they'll lose.
（青峰）このままじゃ負けだな
（さつき）え？
What?
あいつの考えてることなんて
手に取るように分かるぜ
It's obvious what he's thinking.
I'm sure he's wishing he could enter the Zone.
大方“ゾーンに入れば…”
とか思ってんだろ
But at this rate, he'll never enter the Zone.
…が—
このままじゃ 一生かかっても
ゾーンになんざ 入れねえよ
What do you mean?
どういうこと？
It's harder to enter the Zone a second time,
（青峰）ゾーンってのは—
１回目より２回目のほうが
入るのが難しくなる
because you've already experienced it once.
なぜなら一度体感して
知っちまったからだ
Once you learn what it's like for everything to go your way,
あの—
何でも思い通りになるような
状態を知ってしまえば—
you naturally want to experience it again.
自然“もう一度”
という気持ちが湧く
But those are idle thoughts.
けど それは雑念だ
集中状態である
ゾーンに入るために—
That's what you absolutely can't do if you want to enter the focused state of the Zone.
一番あっちゃなんねえもんだ
（青峰）ゾーンに入るためには—
If you want to enter the Zone, you can't try to enter the Zone.
ゾーンに入ろうとしたらダメなのさ
（紫原）えいっ
（火神）がっ！？
（伊月）火神！
Kagami!
Out of bounds! Black ball!
（審判）アウト･オブ･バウンズ！
黒ボール！
Damn it.
くそっ… ん？
何スか その体たらくは
Why do you look so miserable?
黄瀬…
Kise.
（日向）おっ
（黒子）黄瀬君
Kise.
ん？ 黄瀬ちん…
Kise-chin...
あれ？ 知り合いかと思ったら
違ったっスね
Oh? I mistook you for someone I knew.
あんた誰？
Who are you?
あ？ 何…
Huh? What are you—
I don't know any idiots who rely on anything when they play basketball.
知らねえよ
んな 何かにすがって
バスケやるようなヘタレは
Looks like I'll be playing Murasakibaracchi in the semis.
どうやら準決は紫原っちと
やることになりそっスねえ
I look forward to playing you.
よろしくっス
You're right.
そうだね
てか 今 試合中なんだから
あんま話しかけないでよ
Actually, I'm in the middle of a game right now.
Don't talk to me.
I don't know what to say.
（黄瀬）何だかな…
The person I knew was far scarier in our practice game.
こんなんだったら—
練習試合のときの誰かさんのほうが
よっぽど怖かったっスわ
（火神）すがってるだ？
Relying on something?
オレがいつ 何にすがって
バスケしたってんだよ！？
When have I ever relied on anything when playing basketball?
All I could do then was fight recklessly.
あんときは ただ がむしゃらに
戦うことしかできなかった
I was far weaker then, and I couldn't enter the Zone.
体力も 今より
はるかに足りなかったし—
ゾーンに入るなんて
とても無理だった
If anything, that was natural, but I...
むしろ それが当たり前で…
それでも何とか…
火神君？
Kagami?
（火神）黒子
Kuroko, have you ever entered the Zone?
オマエ ゾーンってのに
入ったことあるのか？
（黒子）ゾーン… ですか？
The Zone?
I don't know, but in any case,
分かりませんが とりあえず—
そんなホイホイ入れたら
誰も苦労しません
I don't think it's something that can be entered into that easily.
（火神）フッ… だよな
You're right.
Kagami?
火神？
No matter how much it hurts,
どんなに苦しくても—
Kuroko's
I
Basketball
今できることを
やるしかねえよな！
I just have to do whatever I can now.
Medical Room
うっ… いっ…
イテテッ！
Medical Room
いつ… ぐあっ…
All done!
（リコ）はい おしまい！
（木吉）ハァ…
Now you just have to replenish your nutrients and lie there until the last second.
（リコ）
あとは栄養補給して—
ギリギリまで そこで寝てんのよ！
（木吉）リコ
（リコ）ん？
Riko.
Hm?
Could you stay with me a little longer?
もう少しだけ
そばにいてくんね？
What?! What are you talking about?!
はい！？ 何言ってんの あんた！？
If we don't go soon, the game will be...
早く行かないと試合が…
（木吉）分かってる…
だから１分だけでいい
I know. Just one minute.
何か リコ見てると
元気出んだよね
Looking at you gives me strength.
Could you stop treating me like an idiot?
私のこと バカみたいに言うの
やめてくんない？
I need to recover as much as I can, even if it's just a placebo.
（木吉）今は気休めでも
回復が欲しいんだ
Hyuga and the guys are fine.
日向たちなら大丈夫だ
They'll hang in there until I come back.
オレが戻るまで
絶対 諦めずに持ちこたえてくれる
Besides, Seirin's got a shadow and light supporting the team.
それに…
誠凛にはチームを支える影と—
光がいるからな
（劉(リュウ)）うっ はっ！
（火神）はっ！
Has he always jumped this high?
（劉）こいつ… こんなに
高かったアルか！？
（岡村）ふっ ふぐっ！
（審判）誠凛高校 タイムアウト！
Seirin High, time out!
I've got a message from the coach.
（小金井）カントクからの伝言だ
Kuroko, Hyuga, and Izuki triple-team Himuro.
氷室に黒子 日向 伊月の
トリプルチーム
中に火神 水戸部(みとべ) ２人で対応する
Kagami and Mitobe will handle the inside.
Reduce Kagami's defensive range to the paint.
それに伴い火神の守備範囲は—
ペイントエリアのみに縮小
We may be able to reduce the number of shots from Himuro,
氷室の攻撃回数は
減らせるかもしれないけど—
but we'll suddenly be weak on the inside.
中が一気に手薄になるぞ
If we're not providing enough defense,
いや 下手にまんべんなく
守ろうとするくらいなら—
隙が増えても
目的を絞ったほうがいいと思う
we should focus on our goals, even if it leaves us open.
それはそうだが…
Yeah, but...
Roger that.
了解っス
I couldn't do what Murasakibara's doing.
やっぱ紫原と同じことを
やるってのは無理があった…
Sorry.
すんません
In any case, I'll focus on the paint.
とにかくまずは
ゴール下に集中するんで
Yosen
Seirin
What's gotten into Kagami?
どうしたんだ 急に火神は…？
ボクは むしろいいと思います
I think it's a good thing.
Huh?
何となく—
Kagami seems like him now.
今の火神君は あの人に似ています
（岡村）えい
（岡村）えーい
（火神）ふっ！
（紫原）えいっ
What's going on with Kagami?
（紫原）
どうなってんだ 火神…
His movements have changed.
さっきまでと動きが違う…
We're the ones applying pressure,
（福井）
押してるのは あくまでウチだ
なのに やたら
ヒヤヒヤさせやがる！
but he's giving me the chills.
（火神）でいっ！
（岡村）フンッ！
Oh, come on!
（紫原）ああ もう…
ウザくてしょうがねえ
You're so annoying, I can't stand it!
Crap!
しまった！ 戻れ！
Get back!
It's a counterattack!
（観客）カウンターだっ！
Like him?
（日向）似てる？
（黒子）はい
Yes.
He feels like...
雰囲気というか…
一番ノッてるときの青峰君に
He feels like Aomine when he's on fire.
（火神）ハァ… ハァ… ふっ！
（火神）えいっ！！
（紫原）あああっ
Could it be?
（氷室）まさか…
Kagami!
火神…！
I truly believe Kagami is Seirin's light.
つくづく思います…
火神君は—
誠凛の光だと
ハッ…
やりゃできんじゃねえか
I knew he could do it.
Sorry, thanks for waiting.
（リコ）ごめん お待たせ！
って… えっ どうかしたの？
Did something happen?
Kagami just entered the Zone.
火神がゾーンに入った
He stopped Murasakibara.
紫原を止めたんだ
What?
Hope...
（土田）希望が…
I think we might have hope.
希望が見えてきたかもしれない
How does he generate so much pressure when he's sticking to the paint?
（福井）真ん中に
陣取ってるだけで—
なんて迫力だよ…
（氷室）ヘイ！
Hey!
You think you can stop me?
（氷室）止められるつもりか？
面白い！
Interesting!
He jumped on the first release?!
（小金井）１度目の
リリースタイミングで跳んだ！
（氷室）あっ！？ バカな…
Impossible.
Is he floating?
浮いている！？
ゾーン状態のスーパージャンプ…
A super-jump in the Zone!
This is no ordinary jump!
もはや これは跳躍じゃない
（火神）どりゃああっ
He's like a bird!
（氷室）まるで鳥だ…！
うおお ナイスブロック！
Nice block!
ミラージュシュートを
止めた！
He stopped the Mirage Shot!
Crap! Get back!
やべえ！ 戻れ！
Kuroko!
（火神）黒子！
（黒子）ふっ！
（紫原）なっ…
（福井）スリーだと！？
A three?
すごい
Amazing...
He started heading back before he made the shot.
（日向）決まる前に
もう戻り始めてやがった…
Who is he, Midorima?
こんにゃろ 緑間(みどりま)かよ…！
Give me the ball!
（紫原）よこせ！
（福井）うぅーっ！
（日向）あっ これは…！
This is...
I'll jam it in with full power!
（紫原）フルパワーで
たたき込んでやる！
Take this!
くらえ トールハンマー！
Thor's Hammer!
Impossible!
バカなっ！
This power doesn't just come from being in the Zone.
（黄瀬）これは…
ゾーンによるリミッター解除された
パワーだけじゃない
He's adding power by jumping into the ball.
前方に跳んで
その力も上乗せしてる！
But it's still...
けど それにしても…
Even I'm impressed.
さすがに驚いたぜ
（火神）でやっ！
悪いな
Sorry. I used too much strength.
ちょっと
力入りすぎちまった
くっ… くうぅっ…
Amazing. I can't believe he stopped Muk.
（さつき）すごい！
あのムッ君を止めるなんて…
Only someone in the Zone can stop Kagami now.
今の火神を止められるとしたら—
同じゾーンに入ったヤツだけだろ
陽泉(ようせん)側にも その可能性は
あるんじゃないの？
Doesn't Yosen have that potential as well?
They have Muk and Himuro.
ムッ君とか氷室さんなら…
Maybe, but I don't think so.
かもな
…が おそらく それはねえ
Impossible? What do you mean?
それはない？ どういうことだよ？
I don't completely understand the Zone,
オレもゾーンを—
完全に理解してるわけじゃ
ないっスけど—
but there is something I can say.
１つ断言できることがあるっス
ゾーンに入るための最低条件は—
The minimum requirement for entering the Zone
is that you stake everything on the sport you're playing.
その競技に
すべてをかけていること
Broadly speaking, you have to love basketball more than anything.
平たく言えば—
バスケを何よりも
好きであることっス
けど それは紫原っちに
唯一 欠落しているものでもある
But that's the one thing Murasakibaracchi doesn't have.
資質で言えば—
He may be the most naturally talented of the five of us.
もしかしたら オレたち５人の中で
最強かもしれない
But Murasakibaracchi can't enter the Zone.
それでも 紫原っちは
ゾーンには入れない
What about Himuro?
だったら あの氷室は？
He probably doesn't lack that.
あいつは たぶん
そんな欠落とかねえだろ
彼は まあ…
Him? Well...
それ以前の問題じゃないっスか
悪いけど
I hate to say it, but I think he has his own problem.
A fake on par with Himuro's,
（福井）氷室ばりのフェイク…
or maybe even better?!
下手したらそれ以上…！？
（紫原）うっ… ウソ… だろ！？
You can't be serious.
なんで あとに跳んだオレが
先に落ちてんだよ！？
Why am I falling first when I jumped second?
I've heard of this, but I can't believe anyone can actually do it!
話は聞いたことがある…
けど… 体現できるヤツが
マジでいるなんて…
Air walking!
エアウォーク！
（小金井）うおお すげえ！
いけるよ これ！
Amazing!
We could really win!
なんせ 火神がすごすぎ！
Kagami's too amazing!
Hey! It's too early to celebrate.
（リコ）ちょっと！
（小金井）なっ
はしゃぐのは まだ早いわよ！
But Kagami really is godlike right now.
（伊月）けど… 確かに
今の火神は神がかってる
Yosen
Seirin
We're four points behind with three minutes remaining.
Yosen
Seirin
（日向）残り３分 ４点差…
Yosen
Seirin
少なくとも 今…
At the very least, we're controlling the flow of the game.
流れは確実にウチだ！
What?
Hey, what'd you just say?
ちょ… おい 今 何つった？
だ〜から〜 もういいや
I told you. I've had enough.
オレ やーめた！
I quit. Sub me out.
交代してよ
Don't be ridiculous!
（福井）ふざけんな こら！
いきなり 何考えてんだ テメエ！
What are you talking about?!
I don't understand.
理解に苦しむアル！
I'm not having fun anymore.
（紫原）だってつまんなく
なっちゃったんだもん
ちょっと そこの竹刀取れ
Get me that sword.
（紫原）だってつまんなく
なっちゃったんだもん
I'm going to kill him.
とりあえず殺す
（岡村）今 オマエが抜けたら
勝てるもんも勝てなくなる
If you drop out now, we'll lose a game we could still win.
Are you saying you don't care if we lose?
負けてもいいっちゅうんか
貴様！
Yeah. After all, no one can stop Kagami anymore.
だってもう 誰も火神
止めらんないじゃん
Get a grip, Atsushi!
いいかげんにしろ 敦！
The game's not over yet!
まだ勝負は終わってない！
Ow. It's so annoying when you get hot-blooded.
イッテーな
そういう熱血っぽいのが
一番ウザいんだけど
Besides, you're even more useless against Kagami than me.
そもそも 室ちんなんて—
オレより火神に
歯が立たないじゃん
才能が違うって 分かんないの？
Can't you tell he's better than you?
What do you mean by "Himuro has other problems"?
氷室さんが それ以前って
どういうこと？
Haven't you started to notice?
つうか さつきだって
うすうす気付いてんだろ？
Only the chosen can enter the Zone.
ゾーンに入れんのは
選ばれた人間だけだ
At first I thought he might be able to, but I was wrong.
オレも最初は
“もしや”と思ったが—
やっぱ 違(ちげ)えわ
実力は認める
I'll admit he's good.
He's very close to the five of us.
オレら５人に
限りなく近いと言っていい
But he's no prodigy.
だが それでも秀才止まりだ
いくら強くても—
He's good, but he's only the best an ordinary man can be.
凡人の延長線でしかねえ
どれだけ近づこうが—
No matter how close he gets, he'll never come to this side.
決してこっち側に来ることはねえ
I know.
（氷室）分かってるよ
分かってるよ そんなことは…
I know that.
I've always been jealous of his abilities.
ずっと…
あいつの才能に
嫉妬してきたんだからな
But you have what I desperately want,
なのに…
オレが
喉から手が出るほど—
欲してるものを
持ってる オマエが—
あっさり勝負を
投げようとしている
and you're trying to throw the game.
You're making me crazy with rage. Absolutely crazy.
怒りで気がヘンになるぜ
いいかげん…
Get away from me. That's so annoying.
うわあ 引くわ…
そういうの 心底ウザい
Anyway, I can't believe you're crying.
てか あり得ないわ 泣くとか
I sort of noticed, but I didn't know you felt this strongly.
何となく気付いてはいたけど—
ここまでとは思ってなかったよ
Actually, this is the first time I've been amazed
つうか 初めてだよ
ウザすぎて—
逆にすげえと思うのは
by how much someone repulses me.
I guess I'll stay on the court until the end of the game.
（紫原）しょうがないから—
最後までコートには いてやるよ
Masako-chin...
雅子(まさこ)ちん
I told you to call me Coach!
（荒木）
監督と呼べっつってんだろが！
Could I have a hair tie?
ヘアゴム１個くんない？
They were fighting about something.
（日向）何かモメてたけど
大丈夫か？
Is everything okay?
いや… むしろ逆じゃないスか
No, it's probably the opposite.
今までで一番—
They're more dangerous than ever.
ヤバそうです
kasunda mirai wo kirisaku you ni terasu hikari
Like a shining light that cuts through the hazy future,
musuu no kanousei wo motome
I chase after unlimited possibilities.
Gotta open my eyes
Wake up sabitsuita me ni hi wo tomose
Wake up, light a fire in your tired eyes.
Get up kusubutteru baai ja nainda zettai
Get up! Now's definitely not the time to let it smoulder.
youi sareta risou nante iranai
You don't need to have some big dream.
yuragu koto no nai ishi to
Just an unwavering spirit,
mikansei na chizu de ii kara
and an unfinished map is enough.
asu wo tsukame kono te de
Hold on to tomorrow with these hands!
detarame na rizumu de nurikaete iku kako ni
Regretting a past that's being overwritten by a nonsensical rhythm...
koukai hitotsu arienai daro
That's not possible, right?
ari no mama no biito de kurikaeshite iku genzei wo
I'll rewrite things with the true beat now,
kasaneta mirai kagayaku you ni
and create a sparkling future.
kizami konda sonzai wo kesshou toshite
Your existence is etched as a crystal.
Keep it in my story
Next Episode
Everyone's so annoying.
（紫原）
暑っ苦しくて 嫌になるよ
Why are you playing then?
（黒子）
じゃあ なんで出るんですか？
What?
Because I hate losing even more.
負けるのは もっと嫌だし
I'm the same way.
（黒子）
それはボクも同じです
Episode
Win!
（紫原）
みんな ひねり潰してやるよ
I'll crush you all!